A Guide to the Arena Stage Dramaturgical Files, 1950-2000
George Mason University Libraries
- The Arena Stage Dramaturgical Files
  - paper, "Soviet Medicine" (Box Box 68)
  - behavior in 18th century Russian life (paper) (Box Box 68)
  - An Irish woman's observations of Russian Life (Box Box 68)
  - "A Report on Russian in the 1840's" (Box Box 68)
  - Eckardt's "Russia" (Box Box 68)
  - geography of Russia (Box Box 68)
  - Verradsky's "History of Russia" (Box Box 68)
  - Russian Cooking (Box Box 68)
  - misc. research (Box Box 68)
  - program articles (Box Box 68)
  - Russian Empire Photos (Box Box 68)
  - Set and Costume design research (Box Box 68)
  - "A Month in the Country", freeborn (Box Box 68)
  - "A Month in the Country", actors packet (Box Box 68)
  - "The Match Maker" research and study guide (Box Box 69)
  - "The Match Maker", research and study guide cont. (Box Box 69)
  - "The Mad Dancers", script, research and notes (Box Box 69)
  - "The Waiting Room", research (Box Box 69)
  - "The Waiting Room", research (Box Box 69)
  - "The Waiting Room", research (Box Box 70)
  - "The Waiting Room", research (Box Box 70)
  - "3 Nights in Tehran", final script and research and "The Secret Wife", script (Box Box 70)
  - "Holiday Heart", script and research (Box Box 70)
  - "Holiday Heart", script and research (Box Box 70)
  - "Coming of the Hurricane", script (Box Box 70)
  - "A Mans a Man", actors packet (Box Box 71)
  - "A Mans a Man", draft script (Box Box 71)
  - "Yellowman", script and actors packet (Box Box 71)
  - "Senor Discretion Himself", actors packet (Box Box 71)
  - "Senor Discretion Himself", 1st draft (Box Box 71)
  - "Senor Discretion Himself", script (Box Box 71)
  - "Senor Discretion Himself", vocal score (Box Box 71)
  - "Orpheus Descending", 1st rehearsal (Box Box 72)
  - Battle of Angels (Box Box 72)
  - Battle of Angels - produced first (Box Box 72)
  - "Orpheus Descending" - Draft script (Box Box 72)
  - "Shakespeare in Hollywood", Dramaturgy packet (Box Box 72)
  - "Shakespeare in Hollywood", research (Box Box 72)
  - "Shakespeare in Hollywood", 1st draft (Box Box 72)
  - "Shakespeare in Hollywood" rehearsal draft (Box Box 72)
  - "Proof", actors packet (Box Box 72)
  - "Camelot", actors packet and research (Box Box 73)
  - "Crowns", draft script (Box Box 73)
  - "On the Town", musical score (Box Box 74)
  - "On the Town", conductors score (Box Box 74)
  - "Merrily We Roll Along", musical score (Box Box 74)
  - "Merrily we Roll Along", percussion score (Box Box 75)
  - "Merrily we Roll Along", Bass score (Box Box 75)
  - "Merrily we Roll Along", reed score (Box Box 75)
  - "Merrily we Roll Along", reed score (Box Box 75)
  - "Merrily we Roll Along", trombone (Box Box 75)
  - "Merrily we Roll Along", keyboard score (Box Box 75)
  - "Merrily we Roll Along", trumpet score (Box Box 76)
  - "Merrily we Roll Along", trumpets (Box Box 76)
  - "Happy End", conductor score (Box Box 76)
  - misc. correspondence (Box Box 76)
  - photos of Arena Stage's commissioned playwrights (Box Box 76)
  - Fellows info (Box Box 76)
  - University of the District of Columbia, misc. information (Box Box 76)
  - NEH grant application (Box Box 77)
  - Correspondence, NEH grants (Box Box 77)
  - Arena Stage future plan, 1984 (Box Box 77)
  - Christmas card list 1989 (Box Box 77)
  - "Conquest of the South Pole", mailing (Box Box 77)
  - Scholar records, 1985-1986 season (Box Box 77)
  - scholar records, 1986-1987 season (Box Box 77)
  - scholars program, 1987-1988 (Box Box 78)
  - Resumes for scholars program (Box Box 78)
  - In house readings, 1984-1985 (Box Box 78)
  - Program to "Ibsen: A Voice for the 90's" (Box Box 78)
  - Arena Stage's, "First Review" mailing (Box Box 78)
  - potential readers (Box Box 78)
  - "In the Process '78", report (Box Box 78)
  - DC playwrights, notes (Box Box 78)
  - O'Neill national playwrights conference info (Box Box 78)
  - O'Neill National Playwrights conference (Box Box 78)
  - midwest playwrights program (Box Box 78)
  - FDG/CBS Xerox masters (Box Box 78)
  - New Dramatists - script share (Box Box 78)
  - FDG/CBS new play program (Box Box 78)
  - visiting theatricians (Box Box 79)
  - foreigners and visitors and playwrights (Box Box 79)
  - Audience response (letters) (Box Box 79)
  - special services booklet (Box Box 79)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", horn score (Box Box 80)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", horn score (Box Box 80)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", reed score (Box Box 80)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", reed score (Box Box 80)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", reed score (Box Box 80)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", reed score (Box Box 80)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", extra percussion score (Box Box 80)
  - "It' a Wonderful Life", extra percussion (Box Box 80)
  - "It' a Wonderful Life", reed score (Box Box 81)
  - "It' a Wonderful Life", reed score (Box Box 80)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", percussion score (Box Box 81)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", percussion score (Box Box 81)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", trumpet score (Box Box 81)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", trumpet score (Box Box 81)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", piano score (Box Box 81)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", trumpet score (Box Box 82)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", trumpet score (Box Box 82)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", keyboard score (Box Box 82)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", keyboard score (Box Box 82)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", Trombone score (Box Box 82)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", Trombone score (Box Box 82)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", bass (Box Box 82)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", bass score (Box Box 82)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", conductors score (Box Box 83)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", conductors score (Box Box 83)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", keyboard score (Box Box 83)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", keyboard score (Box Box 83)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", keyboard score (Box Box 83)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", cello score (Box Box 83)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", cello score (Box Box 83)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", script (Box Box 84)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", script (Box Box 84)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", script (Box Box 84)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", script (Box Box 84)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", stage plans and drawings (Box Box 84)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", correspondence (Box Box 84)
  - "It's a Wonderful Life", study guides (Box Box 84)
  - "The Time of Your Life", script (Box Box 85)
  - characteristics (Box Box 85)
  - "The Time of Your Life", rehearsal info (Box Box 85)
  - "The Time of Your Life", script (Box Box 85)
  - "The Time of Your Life", misc. info (Box Box 85)
  - "The Time of Your Life", reviews (Box Box 85)
  - "The Time of Your Life", study guide and program (Box Box 85)
  - "The Time of Your Life", music and photos (Box Box 85)
  - "The Great White Hope", script (Box Box 86)
  - "The Great White Hope", reviews and research (Box Box 86)
  - "Uncle Toms Cabin", study guide (Box Box 86)
  - "The Great White Hope", actors packet (Box Box 86)
  - "The Great White Hope", script (Box Box 86)
  - "K2" script (Box Box 87)
  - "K2", script (Box Box 87)
  - "Agamemnon and his Daughters", draft script (Box Box 87)
  - "Agamemnon and his Daughters", second draft script (Box Box 87)
  - "Agamemnon and his Daughters", final draft script (Box Box 87)
  - "Agamemnon and his Daughters", rehearsal draft script (Box Box 87)
  - "Agamemnon and his daughters", final script (Box Box 87)
  - "Eleanor", script (Box Box 87)
  - "On the Jump", script (Box Box 87)
  - "The Great White Hope", bound script (Box Box 88)
  - "The Great White Hope", unbound script with notes (Box Box 88)
  - "Animal Crackers", misc notes and info (Box Box 88)
  - "Hot 'N' Throbbing", notes (Box Box 88)
  - "The Great White Hope", script (Box Box 88)
  - "Polk County", research and background (Box Box 89)
  - "Polk County", background and research (Box Box 89)
  - "Polk County", script (Box Box 89)
  - "A Moon for the Misbegotten", notes and background information (Box Box 89)
  - "Polk County", script (Box Box 89)
  - "Polk County", script (Box Box 89)
  - "The Way of the World", script and playbill (Box Box 90)
  - "The Way of the World", study guide, playbill and notes (Box Box 90)
  - "The Way of the World", notes, research, partial script (Box Box 90)
  - "Sir Godfrey Kneller and his times: 1646-1723 (Box Box 90)
  - "Notes and Queries" ??? (Box Box 90)
  - "The First English Actress" title page and pictures (Box Box 90)
  - Biographical dictionary of actors (Box Box 90)
  - "The Pageant of Stuart England", photocopies (Box Box 90)
  - "three family formation" (Box Box 90)
  - Arena Stage Program by Margaret Ezell (staff) (Box Box 90)
  - James Boswell and his World (Box Box 90)
  - mafia-something (Box Box 90)
  - The Grand Style (Box Box 90)
  - The English: A social history (Box Box 90)
  - Illustrated English social history (Box Box 90)
  - marriage system in England (Box Box 90)
  - The Court wits of the restoration (Box Box 90)
  - the revolution and the people (Box Box 90)
  - misc. letters and info (Box Box 90)
  - England (Box Box 90)
  - James Boswell and his world (Box Box 90)
  - "She Stoops to Conquer" (Box Box 90)
  - "Modes and Manners", script (Box Box 91)
  - 20,000 years of fashion (Box Box 91)
  - Stratford festival, 1976, program (Box Box 91)
  - The Timetable of history (Box Box 91)
  - "The Comedy of Manners" (Box Box 91)
  - London Life (Box Box 91)
  - The Pageant of London (Box Box 91)